<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-05-16T15:43:04-03:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">IntP - Resource-driven Profiler</title><subtitle>A instrumentation tool to quantify the level of interference an application puts on each hardware’s subsystem.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">About</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/about/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="About" /><published>2018-05-11T00:00:00-03:00</published><updated>2018-05-11T00:00:00-03:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/About</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/about/">&lt;p&gt;IntP measures the amount of noise an application is susceptible and the interference applications causes one another, but also points out which source of noise is more disturbing performance. This instrumentation enables accurate prediction of the performance degradation that results from contention on shared resources. In addition, it provides outputs for better application placement strategies, which makes datacenter resource efficient and more cost effective.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IntP not only quantify the interference application’s tasks cause on hardware resources but also provides insights about application demands during runtime. Since such an application has been instrumented, the users are capable of deciding which piece of hardware is more likely to be the bottleneck and take a decision about the queued application that best interleaves with it. Or if one application starts to affect others, it could be migrated to other machines to minimize interference and maximize performance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;contact&quot;&gt;Contact&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:cesar.derose@pucrs.br&quot;&gt;Prof. Dr. César Augusto Fonticielha De Rose&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:miguel.xavier@pucrs.br&quot;&gt;Prof. Dr. Miguel Gomes Xavier&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">IntP measures the amount of noise an application is susceptible and the interference applications causes one another, but also points out which source of noise is more disturbing performance. This instrumentation enables accurate prediction of the performance degradation that results from contention on shared resources. In addition, it provides outputs for better application placement strategies, which makes datacenter resource efficient and more cost effective.</summary></entry></feed>